god
what now
looks like it was a hanging
we are waiting for forensic experts
to determine time of death
we suspect sexual assault
the closure of the mine made people poor overnight
then he himself was Adam on earth
the prospect of a casino opening in the city has divided people
The 2 sides clashed almost every day
as if they were sworn enemies
as soon as evening came
the streets were filled with drunken hooligans
in a world without law and order
women and children suffered from violence
we were inundated with crime reports
but they kept repeating the same phrases
and there was no real progress
please be patient
we'll fix everything soon
let's go then
she appeared
keep order
ruthless killer
as if mocking us
killed the offenders
in the same manner
in which way they tortured their victims
praying mantis
송규 뜨도다
captain
damn
Mr. Kim Kim Ta Song Song Gyo
sunggyu call the doctor
you can't die
kim you are a dream
I have to save him
you can't die
you can't die chasuyeol please
you should become a police officer
because 5 people died
you can save five
please
아아아
아
eco shade system
don't even dream about it
everyone in prison has the same dream
the missing man was the father of two children
fortunately
he was able to return home safely
thank you
for your help
main condition
which she set for full recognition was
so that you don't suffer any consequences because of her fall
she asked me to change your name and personally
watch you grow
these are my terms
personal space coffee
музыка
books
I made this list of essentials
after much thought
most important
no one needs to know
that jongho is my son
please change his name
including last name
you were worried
missed me
you agreed to help us
provided that I will be present
because we were bored yes
suguan that employee from the district government he is still alive
he knows everything
he knows that you are my son and even knows
that you are probably married
even knows your address
he knows your wife's name
lijunion
she knows about me too
just don't tell me
what did you tell her
I was told this is irgacheffe
your favorite
I only put money in for 1
this is not considered beautiful
I don't think so after all the money
what did she eat from me
ah
I'm glad everything worked out
you did everything yourself
is this a compliment or a reproach?
when suguwan went to the hospital I swear
you were left aside only because
I hope everything was chaotic
you won't misunderstand me
don't worry I don't understand
well captain
what do you think
do you think that suguwan is the culprit of these arson crimes
not sure and you
look at this
his house was in disarray
but this place is clean
like some kind of shrine
and this zero section is only 1 digit and nothing more
this figure cannot be meaningless
All materials about the victims of Chon and Shin were stored here
this could mean
maybe there is 1 more murder of chenna sheena
which we don't know
kill to 1
and you think about
knows how to do this
that's exactly 2 murders
which were before his crime
it is not associated with 1
captain
last time I was wrong
because I got too excited
let me meet oguwan again
Of course I'm not trying to hide it or anything like that
let's go
now
yes restricted area
only with permission
they said when he will wake up
don't know
taking into account the head injury and everything else
Mr. Soguwan
Mr. Dream can you hear me
ceramic studio area
Junyan
you haven't run away yet
Suyul how old
how many winters are there?
no no
leave it alone for a while
I have to go soon
I thought you caught the criminal
Well, for now we need to keep an eye on him
I can't tell you the details
did you eat, eat before you leave
I think I'm fine with food
can you just hug me
no
you will leave as soon as I do this
come hug me
we need to finish this
we have to kill him now he knows everything
kids
this is also a place of trade and study
what have you done here
come up with it all
and your bedroom is right above us
no macaw
that's not true, I have to go
I went oh
no need you don't have to leave
I'll leave you
finish the job
finish properly no
he just came in for a while
Sooyol make sure to eat on time
ok
ok macaw
See you later too, don't give up
good
bye
drive carefully
being a police officer is not easy
the work never ends
but when will this case be closed?
he can rest
maybe we can make some tea
brutal murder cut out tongue
and this section is zero
it's just a number and nothing more
this number can't just happen
hello sir
what are you doing
I told you that today you can leave early
and what
what now
1 victim we didn't know
wait how could suguwan know this not sure
something's wrong
I think we missed something
you mean
that there was a murder
which I didn't know about
damn
I saved it because the handwriting was different
don't be afraid
oh my god why now
어 어 어
어어
어
어 어 어 어
뭐찾아요
this letter was sent by cheny shin
offering help
dear detective why are they written
similar handwriting
doesn't look like sukuwan's handwriting at all but
this is not enough to examine handwriting, but
they are very similar
isn't that why I wanted to check
sir
if
Jeong Yi Shin really wrote this letter
if she finally answered him with words of support
after never answering his letters
this would be a powerful motivation for suguwan
what does she need this for?
for her to receive
if suguwan kills someone
I'm jealous you can come without warning
whenever you want
and I have to meet you
despite my discomfort
they are warm
even after they killed five
or six
what's wrong with you
I'm the same
why did you manipulate suguwan
you were bored
life in prison was too monotonous
there is 1 more
in addition to the original 5 is correct
I already told him everything
told
Saturday he knew about it
boy answer me
before
with which you cut out the chug's tongue and threw his body by the stream
you killed someone else didn't you
These are the questions you should ask detective Chi Joon Ho
I already admitted it a long time ago
Jeon and Shin
whose boss thought
that you could ask for this meeting
to see me
he thought that you
must have missed me during the 23 years of separation
sentimental old man
in prison your life was on a strict schedule
but here everything is different
you're here helping with a copycat murder case
I have the right and duty to interrogate and question you
any time and any day
when I deem it necessary
if you feel so uncomfortable
tell me straight
I can get you back
in the end suguwan is the only one so crazy
to want to see you
that's all for today
someone else died
what's going on
is it related to other murders yes
he's here
hello
walk carefully across the pond
don't touch the evidence
Hansoo measure
take a photo of everything from your body position
victim yushi hyung
42 years old professor at Hyoryong Music College
no criminal record
his whole family lives in Vancouver
he lived in this house 1
and
an injection mark was found on his neck
how many mirrors are there
just like 4 d x
this is probably a message to us
I'm alive and well here
stop chasing
after a certain person and make fools of yourself
kim hyunwoo
hansu chul
Miyosh hyung
cut off tongue
beheading
and now death by drowning
we couldn't save anyone
we couldn't prevent any of this
at the moment
victim identified as college professor
police deny possible link to creek murders
node and in warehouse
but suspicion cannot be dismissed
Mr. Otis, a reporter, was with you
you can give comments
you're the team leader right?
this murder is related to the murder at the creek
nadu captain captain
captain
this murder is related to the creek murder
nadu captain captain
suyeol
Sooyool I just saw you on the news
tell me you haven't seen your mom again
answer me
uh mister jeong
this is junyoung
Suyul is taking a shower now
hey junyoung
understandable
I watched the news and started to worry
nothing serious
I'm sorry
I'll call you back later
yeah ok
smells very tasty
I asked you to wipe yourself dry before leaving
everything is fine
I'll dry quickly
you also have a wound on your hand
dried it well before applying the ointment
otherwise infection may begin
let's do it after dinner
I haven't had dinner at home for a long time
then please
apply ointment to my wound
dear wife dear husband
why do you always come home with a new wound
you're making your dear wife worry technically
I don't get injured every day on the team.
I'm known for my great physique and cat-like agility.
can't you see
and it's not such a serious matter
just a scratch
good
I said everything is really good
like this
honestly I'm fine okay
good
I added peas to rice
I love them very much
음
I'm ready to spread some more
when will you take a shower tomorrow morning
I saw the news
true
the examination has not yet been completed
but the reporters came running to me
you always tell me
that everything is fine
what nonsense is this?
but I'm not at all happy with it
what do I learn about your difficulties
or about your anger through the news
if it's difficult for you
just tell me just tell me
that you are angry and make money on the case
I should know everything too
jeongyeon this feeling
like you're secretly hiding this from me on purpose
I'm really sorry
I just
I didn't want you to worry
it's hard to talk to me
I'm so unreliable for you
that you need to deliberately hide your feelings
and there’s no way to always smile in front of me
I swear it's not like that
I'm sorry I won't do this again
why don't I trust you
you are the only person
who I trust in this world
jeongyeon come on
look at me a
no, look at me
look
look at me
ok come here
I told you to dry your hair properly
so soon you will smell
and what will you do
if they start teasing you and telling you
what are you captain stink
I would like it
I'm fine with the captain stink
eh
crime of arson mantis
Nudu broadcast
Shihondong Pond
victim yushahyun
what is this flashing light
flashlight for self-defense
due to the variety of species and different distribution channels
it cannot be tracked
if he wanted to neutralize someone
a stun gun or taser would be more reliable
he was sure
what will cope with the victim
he distracted him with light
and then hit
is there anything unusual
victim's phone went missing
it's repeating itself
in all cases
there are reasons for that
maybe there's something there
what could give him away
it's yoshahyun his phone is on
1 snow is not always romantic
Looks like the signal is coming from there
it's too easy
I'm not the only one who thinks so
he could have been wrong
let's start an investigation
hyuk, you and I will go left to this house
you two go right let's go
hey hyuk
he never left even a hair at a crime scene
isn't it strange
I dreamed about my late grandmother yesterday
and what about last time
when she appeared
I was wounded, remember?
I have a bad feeling
something needs to be done
give me a check for over 100,000
that's it
get away get out of here
soo yeol tell me
that you haven't seen your mom again
accident on yonpo bridge
security measures
after an accident on the Yonpo Bridge
you scared me I'm sorry
but why are you like this
is anyone home
sorry
my son
guess so
what is this jongho
you love to draw
I did this for you
tadam hold jongho
draw a great portrait
ok great
great how should I pose
I'll just draw what I see
jongho why do you throw so accurately
with powerful rotation
you are so strong
ok I'll throw this very high now
try to catch
abandoned
oh no
he fell into a well
captain
yes detective kim
did you find anything?
he said that she died in this accident
but not a single article mentions that a woman died
so you think his mother is alive
Yes, Mr. Chun's call confirmed this
but there may be mistakes in newspapers
better ask him directly
if you have any questions
but he never mentioned his 7
even when I ask
he avoids answering with a joke
then just leave it with you because everything is fine
it would be different
if only he had started this conversation himself
Lijognon why such a serious face
look
what a pout
come on, get up
just forget about it
forget everything let's move on
help me with brush strokes
I heard his mother was buried
in the city where Suyeol lived as a child
do you want to go there
let's go before you start to worry
it's better yes
that's what it is
he's definitely watching us
where is the truth from?
why do you think that
he mocks us
he probably
I like to watch us suffer
that's his goal
hey you're having fun
rotten bastard
what's going on
nothing
What time are you not hungry?
let's finish this
let's go through it again
it's too late you're still unhappy captain
you can say that
if something seems wrong
It's worth driving through again, remember
how did he find kim te-juk last time
let's do 1 more lap
if we don't find anything
then let's move on
sir
maybe it doesn't mean anything
but in the kitchen of the house next door
we're not in the yard
isn't it strange
that this clay jug is just standing in the room
also with some kind of red puck inside
I probably said nothing
by chance
Has anyone seen something like a well nearby?
the house looks like this
like it was built a long time ago
this town was clearly under construction
that means wells
should be here
but I haven't seen any here
Probably removed when the water supply was installed
probably fixed it just in case
they just wouldn't have removed it if they saw it
maybe it was him, I saw something when we arrived
look over there
help me
times 2 3
welcome
you finally found it
national investigative service
Looks like a different weapon was used here
than when wounded in the back
maybe a blade
everyone has gathered
yes his name is jung won shik
he suddenly disappeared 3 months ago
he was a developer in this company DJ Salushen
in the early 2000s
when the agency digitized criminal cases
his company was involved in this
this means his company had access to their materials
yeah it looks like the criminal used jung won shik
to get data from jeong and shin
which only the police had
hello hello, take a seat
that means the wannabe lad is madam
long time no see
hi dear
and I haven't seen you for a long time
soool you work so hard here
but at least be home sometimes okay
Madam, leave family quarrels for later
that they found the official cause of death
multiple stab wounds
judging by the condition of the body
death occurred at least 0 months ago
3 months
if 3 months ago it was before the murder on the creek note
well that's what's really strange
the traces of the hold show that the victim was already immobilized
but it’s strange too
that the stab wounds in the back seemed to have been inflicted impulsively
it doesn't look like it was a dagger
more like fabric scissors
but wounds on the chest and neck
look like
they were drawn almost playfully
as if the attacker was playing with him
while he was dying of blood loss
it’s strange isn’t it, the imitator is young
there are no matches
indicating imitation
him hyung with his tongue cut
hansu chul in the warehouse
and the drowned man Yushi hyung
this is all for sure
copycat murders
copying chyonyshen
however jung won shik no
he's completely different
what if this is his 1st murder
he could impulsively stab the victim in the back first
before using jeong's methods and imitating her style
that would mean
that he tasted blood here
and then he followed in the footsteps of Chong and Shen
but none of the murders are chong and shen
was never connected to the body in the well
sir
we found this at soguwan see
section zero is empty
soguwan collected all this material about cheny shin
to create something like a sanctuary
2nd murder 1 more man killed in Unsan
4 serial murder 5 murder
mustion
하하하하하
하
ㅎㅎ
으하하하
으하하하 으하하하하
you like to come at this hour yes
can we be alone
my father did it
it was him
yes
I did it
it was the best
what did I do in life
I still think so
how could you sacrifice your husband like that?
he was my father
but thanks to this you managed to survive
that was the most important thing to me
everything is fine
stop talking nonsense
you killed my father
so that I live for my sake
shame on you
how can you make such disgusting excuses
that's not an excuse
you probably
don't remember this
but that man was always drunk
he got drunk that day too
back where is jongho
he sleeps already late
this damn boy should be here
to meet my father
leave him he fell asleep late okay
what happened
the house smells or something
come up here
hey stop it
sit here
yeah ok
ok I heard you
don't shout or you'll wake him up no
forget get up
get up get up come on
you know yes you know
how much I really appreciate you
yes I know
I know thanks
but it's too late
you need to sleep
I'll clean up here and be back soon
so good
god
it was one of the miners
how can you say that
probably when I was cleaning the kitchen
the smell stuck to me
these soot-covered bastards cross the bridge with dirty thoughts
their eyes widen and they go crazy
when they see women in the city
you thought I don't know
take off your clothes
here
no one comes to us
you're wrong
take off your clothes if you have nothing to hide
if I find at least 1 soot stain on you
hurry up before I tear it all down myself
ok ok
let's go to our room
not here
let's go to the room
I'll undress there
why do you want to go inside so bad
damn it
what were you doing here anyway?
what are you hiding
oh you're disgusting
yeah there's nothing here
I'm not hiding anything
stop it stop it
Chunko go back to the room
dad and mom talking
stop tormenting your mom
here's the boy
are you sure he's mine
stop it dear
come here dear bastard
please stop moving
darling I'll teach you a lesson darling
please no please no oh you
come out come here little one
how dare you
sorry daddy scoundrel
you are kim jong ho dad
you're definitely kim
you are my scoundrel son
you only know how to talk, lie down on the floor, you little devil
you dared to snap at your father, you brat
get it, stop that rubbish
아아
아
중국어
luckily you weren't too hurt
you passed out from shock
you're lying
everything is foggy
but I remember everything, my dad
he made me a desk
and played ball with me
oh yeah
he had his moments
once every 100 years
when he wasn't drunk
why at all
you hid it
when she confessed to her crimes
how can you consider yourself human
you justify your crimes with your child
why did you hide it until now
why the hell
you did it
no one asked about it that's all
that you couldn't remember
what happened that day
I said that he left us for another woman
and everyone just didn’t discuss it
Is this my fault?
I watched it before
how cats hunt birds
when I was little
birds couldn't fly
but they didn’t die either
for them birds are not food
when a bird with a broken wing or other injury
tried to move again
the hunt continued
but in the end she dies
so you need to save her right before that
if a child wants to save a bird
you have to be careful
if you squeeze her too hard she will die
light pressure on the sternum
and it breaks like this
they are so fragile
but you know people are not that different
my husband
dead
killing a person is very easy
the whole problem is to get rid of the body and remove everything
this is
just hard work
it's so difficult
then I realized it
killing someone is easy
it’s difficult to eliminate the consequences and clean everything up
but that day
I'm very lucky
하하
I just killed it and it started to rain
that's how I found peace
and Jung Ho and I
were happy together
you were calm
after that
you were able to kill
five more
they deserved to die
no you killed just because
that I wanted to kill
after his 1st kill
after my father's murder
you must have developed a thirst for blood
or am I wrong
I can't deny it
you
butcher enjoying the smell of blood mantis
just a monster
yes
that day
I shouldn't have done that
I'm just lucky
it started to rain, I couldn’t finish everything
because I was so worried about you
I had to tear off 1 of each of his limbs
his head would be the last one to shut up
he had to watch his body being torn apart
I messed up because it was the first time
I messed up so bad
that she didn’t even want to tell the police
please just stop
just shut up
that's enough
how
how can you be so cruel
yes I killed your father
I cut out the rotten bastard's tongue
broke another's neck and turned his joints
1 more hydrogen mash
I did it
you hate me
I'm disgusting to you
you want to kill me
it would be easier for you to live
if I just disappeared
kill me you should just kill me
I'm disgusting to you
yeah isn't it
how nice it would be
if I just disappeared
come on come kill me
just kill me right now
my dear son
such a burden for you
stop that your mother is still alive
으아
do you remember any of them
dad what are you doing
you are Jeong and Shin's sister-in-law
you know jeon and shin
and even in the hospital
who is the god of investigations
he's always right
jongho machine park ninjae
now standing in front of my house
she's going to kill
why does jung woo shin want to kill you
this bastard has been watching me and jeongyeon this whole time
you killed them you killed them all yes